

Cátia Torrinha

6 years experience in data analysis and visualization, digital marketing and reporting.

16 years of experience in graphic and web design, namely vector design, paging, websites, and corporate identity.

14 years experience in administration, billing, and accounting.

Very responsible and an active listener.

Professional Experience

Rates Analyst | Global Rates & Codes / Commercial Ops

iBASIS, Portugal, S.A. July 2022

Update supplier and customer rates for Voice Service, ensure rate data are correctly reflected in the systems, maintain supplier and customer account data in the database, research inquiries from both internal and external customers on rate variances, and analysis tasks as needed.

Data & Reporting Consultant | Designer

Impact Transition, Lda. Oct 2021 - Jun 2022

Data Analysis and reporting; developing Business Plans and marketing strategies; creating and editing content for social media and websites.

Data Center Operator

Outware, Concepção Sist. Informáticos, Lda. Oct 2019 - Sep 2021

Dashboard's weekly update; developing reports in Power BI; data processing; creating and editing advertising formats in internal databases, and brand segmentation reclassification.

Marketing Assistant | Web Designer

Smile Bath, S.A. Feb 2019 - Aug 2019

Online store management and social media; performance analysis; national and international customer support.

Designer | Office Clerk

Espaço A3, Lda. Feb 2018 - Feb 2019

Corporate image development; maintenance and updating of company's website; financial and administrative services.

Graphic Designer

Miguel A. Simões, Lda. Aug 2017 - Nov 2017

Corporate image development; maintenance and updating the company's website and newsletters.

Backoffice Assistant

NOWO, S.A. Mar 2010 - Aug 2017

Database update; Insertion of orders and contracts, customer and operational support.

935 922 571 cstorrinha@gmail.com <u>DataCamp</u> <u>LinkedIn</u>

Education

Escola de Tecnologias Inovação e Criação (ETIC)

Level 5 Professional Diploma in Design & Multimedia 2006

Audio & video treatment, layouts and interfaces development, interactive contents development, online and offline environment project development

Escola de Tecnologias Inovação e Criação (ETIC)

Level 5 Professional Diploma in Graphic Design 2005

Vectorial drawing, advertisement (outdoor and mupi), corporate identity, packaging, paging

Escola Secundária Sebastião da Gama

12th Year - Arts 2003

Training

CESAE Digital

Data Analyst - SQL 2024

CECOA

Database Management Systems (DBMS) -Access 2023

IEFP

Excel - Advanced Features 2023

Udemy

Python for Finance: Investment Fundamentals & Data Analytics 2022

Coursera

UX/UI Fundamentals and Digital Marketing 2019

Technologies

- Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, Power Point, and Access)
- Power BI | Tableau
- Jira Software
- SQL Server Management Studio
- Smartsheet
- Wordpress
- Trello | Planable
- Google Analytics | Google Tag Manager
- · Google Search Console
- · Adobe Creative Suite
- Sendinblue | MailChimp
- Primavera
- Corel Draw
- Quark Express
- Macromedia Flash & Dreamweaver

Hard Skills

- · Data Entry and Analysis
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- A/B Testing
- SaaS | CRM
- Bookkeeping
- · Digital Marketing

Soft Skills

- Responsible
- Professionalism
- · Fast learning
- Adaptable

Languages

- Portuguese Native
- · English Good

935 922 571 cstorrinha@gmail.com <u>DataCamp</u> <u>LinkedIn</u>